<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<challenge>
    <title>New Challenge 5</title>
    <author>
        Andreas Venieris,
        Konstantinos Papapanagiotou,
        Anastasios Stasinopoulos,
        Vasilios Vlachos,
	Rajat Moury
        Alexandros Papanikolaou
    </author>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
         Your school has organized a Trip to Dawki, a beautiful town in Jaintia Hills district, Meghalaya, India. They have maintained the records on the college's INTRANET web-server system on a database, they have not maintained a hard copy of it either. Being short of money one of your best friends "tripjeet" couldn't join the trip, so you have to get into the web-server system through a website vulnerability and edit the database, which might need admin privileges, so that the status for ur friend is "PAID" in the database. The web-developer has tried to filter the requests to an extent, you'll have to get past this. This is sort of illegal, but YOU CAN'T ALWAYS BE ETHICAL. Let's make it more interesting, school-server has been compromised before and according to them, they have taken care of it, they have ask you to run a test, but they are not giving u access to the database or admin privileges ! You have managed to get one information i.e. the backdoor is still  on the server system, so u have to edit the payload to get into the system, get a connection and change the information on the database and clear all the logs. The payload file WAS "backdoor.php". Give it a try ! </p><br/><br/>

Hints /Tips & Rules :
Play with inputs, notice the changes carefully on the web page. You would have to analyse the backdoor that is  weakly encrypted, and enter ur ip  address in the payload for getting reverse connection or for accessing the server system. ".txt" cannot be executed so, might have to play with some extensions </p><br /> For better  understanding, go through these references <a href = "https://www.offensive-security.com/metasploit-unleashed/exploits/">reference1</a><br/> <a href = "http://insecurety.net/?p=403">reference2</a><br/>
]]>

    </description>
</challenge>
