<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<challenge>
    <title>New Challenge 3</title>
    <author>
        Andreas Venieris,
        Konstantinos Papapanagiotou,
        Anastasios Stasinopoulos,
        Vasilios Vlachos,
        Alexandros Papanikolaou
    </author>
    <category>web</category>
    <description>
        <![CDATA[
         You have gotten hold of a hacker's pc, by which he has recently attacked on the target web-server and was having persistent control over the web-server. However, he is refusing to give away how he did that. So, you have to try to hack into this website, check out for any backdoor installed on the web-server, close that listening backdoor connection and log in with sudo/su permission, keep note of the service and port of the backdoor. Also, working as a team your colleague have managed to get hold of the backend-blacklist of the server, here is the file : <a href = "inside/blacklist.txt">blacklist</a> there is a very-minute mistake which all lead to this attack, crack that to get into the web-server and to get sudo credentials of hacker's system which is as defined : "login page" [the hacker's sudo page] is somewhere hidden on the main webpage, this trick works quite sometimes but is a bad habit for web-developers hiding a link. The hacker being assaulted gives hint for his system's su password, "you'll get the login crendentials with the services and port of the backdoor, username is "root" and password is the concatenation of these three words [the hackers speak for the corresponding port number] + [the service running] + [sudo password from the etc/passwd file, shadow crack]". Now, it's time for you to work on, All the Best ! </p><br/><br/>

Hints /Tips & Rules :
You are not allowed to view the source-code of php files (using cat or some other services) , after getting into the web-server system [to kinda make this more challenging]. First check out how the website works by varying different inputs, next go through the blacklist file which with some modifications would allow you to execute commands on the web-server system. You might have to change permissions of files. </p><br /><a href = "https://www.exploit-db.com/papers/13045/">reference1</a><br/>
]]>

    </description>
</challenge>
